<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existing mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="138390" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Adjust Transit Capacity" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Scale Public Transit depots, Passengers, and increase Transit Line slider limits." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
### Adjust Transit Capacity (ATC)

Everything is OPTIONAL!

#### Features
- **Transit depots:** change max vehicles per depot (Bus, Ferry, Subway, Taxi, Tram, Train)
- **Passengers:** change maximum seats (Bus, Tram, Train, Subway, Ship, Ferry, Airplane)
- **Extend Transit Lines:** optional toggle to expand the in-game slider ( if you want just 1 bus on a line or more buses, etc.)

### Notes рџљЌрџљ‹рџљ†вњ€пёЏрџљў
- *Adjust Sliders* at any time, no restart needed; supports switching cities.
- *Depot capacity* = maximum number of vehicles a single depot can maintain/spawn (extension building not scaled).
- Avoid other depot/passenger capacity mods to avoid conflicts (they override each other).
- No Harmony patch or Reflection used; less likely to break on patch days.
- Safe to remove any time (use Reset buttons to return to vanilla game values).
- The transit line feature follows the gameвЂ™s own route logic, so the maximum is variable rather than a fixed static cap.
- On tested routes this can go as low as **1** vehicle and much higher than vanilla on the upper end.


### Important note
- ATC still works fine for players who only want Transit features.
- New mod Public Works Plus includes all ATC plus 5 new major features combined.
- If installing PwP, then remove ATC (since ATC is included in PwP).
- ATC will get minor updates, but major new features will be in PwP.

#### Settings file
- **new settings file**: `ModsSettings/AdjustTransit`
- Older saved settings from earlier ATC do **not** carry over, just set the sliders again and you are good to go.

### Support and feedback
- If the mod helps you, give it a Like, it's free + easy :)
- Feedback on: Github, Discord, etc., links on this page.

### Credits
- River-Mochi: author
- yenyang: code review and testing.
- The transit section is inspired by Wayz's original Depot Capacity Changer.
- Necko1996: testing
- BugsyG: testing

### Performance
This is designed to *not* run in the city per-frame. Player makes changes in Options Menu > then mod goes idle.

### 11 Languages

- English, FranГ§ais, Deutsch, EspaГ±ol, Italiano, Polski Polish, PortuguГЄs Brazilian
- н•њкµ­м–ґ, ж—Ґжњ¬иЄћ, з®ЂдЅ“дё­ж–‡ (Simplified Chinese), з№Ѓй«”дё­ж–‡ Traditional Chinese

### Tip:
If you want to increase transit route slider a little more, add some stops to the route.
Game auto-increases the max based on different factors, adding stops is just the easiest to nudge it.


tags: city dispatch, transit line increase, control municipal, public transit system, change size, increase people passengers, depot size demand, decrease passengers

</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail-ATC.jpg" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image10-TransitOnly.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image20-Passengers.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/adjust-transit-capactiy.1866178/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.3.5" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!-- Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset -->
<ChangeLog>
- Added ferry support to depot and passenger controls.
- uses a new settings file ModsSettings/AdjustTransit; older saved settings do not carry over, just set your sliders again.
- optional Extended Transit Lines toggle.
- Added conflict prevention for Extended Transit Lines in case BOTH ATC and Public Works Plus mod is accidentally installed.
- ATC remains available for players who only need transit-only; Public Works Plus mod includes ATC plus newer features.

</ChangeLog>







	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/PublicWorksPlus/tree/atc-mod" />
</Publish>
