<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existing mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="138390" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Public Works Plus" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Scale Transit, Passengers, Industry Deliveries + Cargo, Road + Parks vehicles, and increase Transit Line slider limits." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
### Public Works Plus (PWP)

**Big update to Delivery Trucks in 2.1.0**


Everything is OPTIONAL - you choose!

- Scale many aspects for:
- all Public Transit + Passengers
- Industry Delivery vehicles, Cargo stations, Extractors.
- Parks/Roads Maintenance

**NEW Company Deliveries will now actually use the increase truck/van amounts you set, reducing traffic with fewer trips.**
Storage Transfers are also improved. Future: other dispatch paths may be improved (more research needed).

### Features
- Transit Line adjuster: can allow as low as 1 bus or higher ~30-60 buses (tram, train, etc.).
- **Parks + Roads Repairs**: fleet size, work shift + rate
- Road wear (beta): scale speed roads accumulate damage over time
- **Industry Deliveries**: scale capacity of delivery vehicles (Semi trucks, Delivery vans, Motorbike, Raw material trucks - coal, oil, etc.)
- *Extractor companies*: max fleet size (usually semi trucks for Fish, Grain, Vegetables, etc.)
- *Cargo Stations*: max active transporters (harbor/train/airport)

#### Complete ATC features included

- **Transit depots:** change max vehicles per depot (Bus, Ferry, Subway, Taxi, Tram, Train)
- **Passengers:** change maximum seats (Bus, Tram, Train, Subway, Ship, Ferry, Airplane)
- Includes everything from *Adjust Transit Capacity* (ATC) mod plus all new mods above are *combined* into one PwP mod.


### Notes 🚍🚋🚆✈️🚢
- *Remove* "Adjust Transit Capacity" if you install this mod.
- *Adjust Sliders* at any time, no restart needed; supports switching cities.
- Avoid other depot/passenger capacity mods to avoid conflicts (they override each other).
- No Harmony or Reflection used; more compatible - less likely to break on patch days.
- Safe to remove any time (use Reset buttons to return to vanilla game default values).
- ✅ Transit Line checkbox: Pick only one mod to adjust this - Don't use other mods that also adjust the in-game slider. There may be conflicts if you also have Transit Policy Adjuster or Smart transportation.
If both are enabled, it's not going to explode, it may be inconsistent like two people changing the radio station.
- How PwP Transit lines is different: follows the game’s method (travel time + stops); you can have just 1 bus per line or ~30-60+ buses (see before/after screenshot).
PwP is made differently; no Harmony patch used and maximum is not static (will not be 250 buses on one line). You still get many more buses per each route line than game vanilla gives.


### Support and feedback
- If the mod helps you, give it a Like, it's free + easy :)
- This mod is 5 new mods combined +ATC; feedback was to combine more features into a single mod.
All details not above might be answered in forums or in tool tips of the mod menu.
- Feedback on: Github, Discord, Forum links on this page.

### Credits
- River-Mochi: author
- yenyang: code review and testing.
- The Transit section is inspired by Wayz's original Depot Capacity Changer.
- Necko1996: testing
- BugsyG: testing

### Performance advantage
This is designed to *not* run in the city per-frame. Make changes in Options Menu > then mod goes idle. Debug tools are optional.

### 11 Languages

- English, Français, Deutsch, Español, Italiano, Polski Polish, Português Brazilian
- 한국어, 日本語, 简体中文 (Simplified Chinese), 繁體中文 Traditional Chinese

### Tip:
If you want to increase maximum of the transit route slider a little more, add some stops to the route.
Game auto-increases the max based on different factors, adding stops is just the easiest to nudge.


tags: city dispatch, transit line increase, control municipal, public transit system, change size, increase people passengers, depot size demand, decrease passengers,
delivery trucks vans, industry semi-trucks, cargo station depot capacity, Extractor fish

</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail-PublicWorksPlus.jpg" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image10-Transit.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/image15-PwP-Before-After.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image20-Passengers.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image30-Industry.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image40-Maintenance.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/image50-Senryu-PwP.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/public-works-plus.1910233/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="2.1.1" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!-- Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset -->
<ChangeLog>
- added logging utils, improved logging reliability.
- no gameplay changes, just internal.
</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/PublicWorksPlus" />
</Publish>
